Calvin Tomkins Papers
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series II: Major New Yorker Articles, 1961-2006
  - Subseries II.A: Research Files, 1961-2006
    These files represent all the major articles Tomkins wrote at The New Yorker with a few exceptions. Materials gathered for the Profiles on Robert Rauschenberg and Marcel Duchamp are scant and are likely to have been moved to the research files for the books on those subjects. The research materials for Living Well is the Best Revenge, a book on Sara and Gerald Murphy, have been withheld by Tomkins; the research materials for the Profile that led to the book are likewise absent.
    Folders are organized in chronological order by date of article publication. The length of time between the start of research and publication varied from three months to two or more years. Within the folders, material has been left in original order. Newsprint has been photocopied and discarded, acidic and fragile materials have been isolated, and extant photographs and slides have been given special housing. The few computer disks that are present were left in the folders but their contents were printed out (in all cases the disks only contained drafts of the articles sent to, or returned by, the magazine.) Original folder titles have been noted where they differ from the article subject and the folders themselves photocopied when information was inscribed on them.
    The folder titles below list the department under which the article was published, the article title, and the general subject. The date noted in the right-most column is the date of article publication, not the date of the research materials.
    - Profile: "Beyond the Machine," Jean Tinguely, 2/10/1962; 1 ALS Jean Tinguely-CT (4/28/1961) 1 ACS Jean Tinguely-CT (n.d.) 1 TLS Julia Ris-CT (4/4/1961) [re: reminiscences of Tinguely when he was a student in art school and Ris was a teacher] 1 ALS Niki de Saint-Phalle-CT (n.d.) [re: Tinguely's preparations for an exhibition at the Louisiana Museum of Modern Art in Denmark] 1 ALS Jean Tinguely-CT (n.d.) 1 TCS Peter Selz-CT (2/12/1962) [re: congratulations on Profile] Invitation, press releases and other documents from first exhibition of Tinguely at the Staempfli Gallery, news clippings, draft typescript with hand edits (n.d.) One-sheet program for performance of The Tinguely Machine Mystery… by Kenneth Koch (Larry Rivers, John Ashberry, and Niki de Saint-Phalle are among the listed performers) Transcript of taped interview (n.d). (Box 12, Folder II.A.1)
    - Profile: "Beyond the Machine," Jean Tinguely, 2/10/1962; Tear sheets of Profile and later materials on Tinguely including bound, photocopied book of recollections by Niki de Saint-Phalle (after 1991). (Box 12, Folder II.A.2)
    - Profile: "Beyond the Machine," Jean Tinguely, 2/10/1962; [Original folder title "Homage New York"] 1966 newspaper from the Modern Museet, Stockholm, printed tirade against Tinguely and Homage to New York. (Box 12, Folder II.A.3)
    - Profile: "Beyond the Machine," Jean Tinguely, 2/10/1962; [Original folder title "Kinetic Show Motion Show (Other Motion Artists)"] Brochure for "Le Mouvement" exhibition, Galerie Deniseren (1955), brief typescript article, "Artists and Machines" by J.R. Pierce 1 ALS Harry Bertoia-CT (3/27/1961) [re: making kinetic art]. (Box 12, Folder II.A.4)
    - Profile: "A Thing Among Things," Richard Lippold, 3/30/1963; [Original folder title "Lippold-Philharmonic"] 1 TLS Walter Gropius-CT (12/4/1962) [re: thanks for Lippold Profile] 1 TL CT-Robert Lippold (4/28/1962) [re: suggesting Profile]Tear sheets of Profile; pamphlets on Lippold, newspaper and magazine clippings on Lippold and contemporary sculpture; list of expenses for article; annual reports for Lincoln Center, 1962 and 1963, and invitation to Lippold sculpture dedication. (Box 12, Folder II.A.5)
    - A Reporter at Large: "The Last Skill Acquired," Dyslexia, 9/14/1963; Newspaper and magazine articles on Dyslexia; two unpublished articles by Norman Geschwind, then professor of neurology, Harvard School of Medicine; transcript of CBS program, "Dyslexia: The Invisible Handicap" (5/18/1980). (Box 12, Folder II.A.6)
    - A Reporter at Large: "The Last Skill Acquired," Dyslexia, 9/14/1963; [Original folder title: "Orton"] 1 ALS June (Mrs. Samuel T.) Orton-CT (12/9/1962) [re: reminiscences of Dr. Orton] Offprints, research notes and interview glosses and transcriptions of Sally B. Childs and Ann Gillingham. (Box 12, Folder II.A.7)
    - A Reporter at Large: "The Last Skill Acquired," Dyslexia, 9/14/1963; [Original folder title: "Orton"] Correspondence exchange with Regine F. Wohlmann (1/14/1963) [re: billing and payment for unsuccessful collaboration on article] 1 TLS Albert J. Harris-CT (4/14/1962) [re: reading education] Research notes, expenses, typescript article, Arthur I. Gates, "What We Know And Can Do About the Poor Reader". (Box 12, Folder II.A.8)
    - A Reporter at Large: "The Last Skill Acquired," Dyslexia, 9/14/1963; Offprints of article, draft typescript with autograph edits and suggested edits by Claude B. Dufault. (Box 12, Folder II.A.9)
    - Profile: "Woomera has It!," John R. Pierce, 9/21/1963; [Original folder title "Echo"] Chronology of Echo program (a satellite program preceding Telstar), note sheets, clippings, press releases and fact sheets from Bell and NASA. (Box 12, Folder II.A.10)
    - Profile: "Woomera has It!," John R. Pierce, 9/21/1963; [Original folder title "Telstar"] Expense notes, biographical notes on scientists and officials, articles and clippings 1 TLS W.H. Pickering-CT (4/2/1963) [re: Profile on Pierce]. (Box 12, Folder II.A.11)
    - Profile: "Woomera has It!," John R. Pierce, 9/21/1963; 1 TLS John Pierce-CT (7/5/1963) [re: revisions to Profile] 1 TLS John Pierce-CT 10/4/1963) [re: responses to publishing] Tear sheet of Profile. (Box 12, Folder II.A.12)
    - Profile: "Moving Out," Robert Rauschenberg, 2/29/1964; Tear sheet of Profile only.; Interview notes and other materials gathered for this article were later dispersed by CT among the files of Series IV.C. (Box 12, Folder II.A.13)
    - Profile: "Figure in an Imaginary Landscape," John Cage, 11/28/1964; Tear sheet of Profile, typescript draft with hand edits, expense report, more recent articles and clippings. (Box 12, Folder II.A.14)
    - Profile: "Figure in an Imaginary Landscape," John Cage, 11/28/1964; 1 TLS Aaron Copland-CT (1/1/1964) [re: request for interview for Cage Profile] 1 ALS Crete Cage (John's mother)-CT (2/6/1964) News clippings, programs and offprints, list of contacts and bibliography. (Box 12, Folder II.A.15)
    - Profile: "Not Seen And/Or Less Seen," Marcel Duchamp, 2/6/1965; Tear sheet of Profile only.; Materials gathered for this article were later dispersed by CT among the files of Series IV.D. A 44-page transcript of an interview between CT and Duchamp in 1964 is located in folder IV.D.29. (Box 12, Folder II.A.16)
    - Profile: "In the Outlaw Area," R. Buckminster Fuller, 1/8/1966; Tear sheets of Profile, draft typescript (12/12/1965), CT's tear sheets from reprint of article on Fuller in another magazine (Saturday Evening Post?). (Box 13, Folder II.A.17)
    - Annals of Law: "The Lewis and Clark Case", 10/29/1966; Tear sheets of article, draft typescript with hand edits (2/9/1965). (Box 13, Folder II.A.18)
    - Annals of Law: "The Lewis and Clark Case", 10/29/1966; 1 ALS, TL copy Mrs. Vaclav Vytlacil-TNY (11/15/1966) [re: correcting factual errors in published article] 1 ALS Mary Hyde-CT (11/4/1966) 1 TCS "Kinkead"-CT (4/28/1964) [re: note of approval to CT from TNY to go ahead with article ] Research notes, interview glosses and transcripts, and summaries of court transcripts. (Box 13, Folder II.A.19)
    - Profile: "The Creative Situation," Eric Hoffer, 1/7/1967; 8 ALS Eric Hoffer-CT (9/9/1966-9/29/1967) 1 photocopy ALS Eric Hoffer-Jack Macrae (4/17/1966) 1 photocopy ALS Eric Hoffer-William Shawn (1/11/1967) [incl. attached note to CT from Shawn] 1 TLS Selden Osborne-CT (1/12/1967) [re: publication of Profile, the Osborne family is discussed in the article] 2 ALS Lili Fabilli Osborne-CT (1/17/1967, 4/17/1968) [re: publication of Profile, suggestion of compensation from later book] Transcripts of CBS News Special with Eric Sevareid "Eric Hoffer: The Passionate State of Mind" (9/19/1967) and KQED program, "Conversations With Eric Hoffer" (n.d.), list of Hoffer's book sales from Harper & Row. (Box 13, Folder II.A.20)
    - Profile: "The Creative Situation," Eric Hoffer, 1/7/1967; 1 ALS Lili Osborne-CT (4/17/1968) Tear sheets of Profile, press photo of Hoffer, Profile Description suggestion (3/28/1966), expenses. (Box 13, Folder II.A.21)
    - Profile: "The Very Rich Hours of Joe Levine," Joseph E. Levine, 9/16/1967; Tear sheets of Profile, photocopy draft typescript with hand edits (3/15/1967) Calendar of MoMA Film Library, films donated by Levine, 1965, clippings articles and offprints, publicity photo still of Levine, official Profile of Levine from Embassy Pictures Corp. (Box 13, Folder II.A.22)
    - Profile: "A Certain Attitude Toward Change," Samuel B. Gould, 12/18/1967; [Original folder title "Education, Misc."] Various news clippings, press releases, and magazine articles on higher education, offprint of TNY article on Berkeley by Calvin Trillin, research notes. (Box 13, Folder II.A.23)
    - Profile: "A Certain Attitude Toward Change," Samuel B. Gould, 12/18/1967; [Original folder title "State University of N.Y. at Stony Brook"] Pamphlets, offprints, press releases, news clippings on the school. (Box 13, Folder II.A.24)
    - Profile: "A Certain Attitude Toward Change," Samuel B. Gould, 12/18/1967; [Original folder title "SUNY-General"] Pamphlet and programming schedule of "New York Network"; news clippings, brochures, press releases and offprints relating to the state university and advances in higher education. Many news clippings have hand annotations. (Box 13, Folder II.A.25)
    - Profile: "A Certain Attitude Toward Change," Samuel B. Gould, 12/18/1967; Typescript address, "Whose Goals for Higher Education," given by Gould (10/12/1967), correspondence with various officials for article, expenses, research notes. (Box 13, Folder II.A.26)
    - Profile: "A Certain Attitude Toward Change," Samuel B. Gould, 12/18/1967; Tear sheets of Profile, typescript draft with hand edits(11/28/1966). (Box 13, Folder II.A.27)
    - Profile: "A Certain Attitude Toward Change," Samuel B. Gould, 12/18/1967; [Original folder title "Internatl. Studies Center" and "Mr. Calvin Tomkins"] Two reports on the development of international studies at the state university, one titled, "Unity in Diversity," by Dr. Glenn A. Olds. (Box 13, Folder II.A.28)
    - Profile: "An Appetite for Motion," Merce Cunningham, 5/4/1968; Pamphlets, programs, tear sheets of other articles, clippings (up to 1996) and expenses. (Box 14, Folder II.A.29)
    - Profile: "An Appetite for Motion," Merce Cunningham, 5/4/1968; Negative filmstrips, 1 photograph, 2 contact sheets, all of Cunningham troupe in practice; tear sheets of Profile, typescript draft (10/9/1967). (Box 14, Folder II.A.30)
    - Onward and Upward with the Arts: "E.A.T.", 10/3/1970; Draft typescript with hand edits (n.d.), copyright assignment document, erratum slip. (Box 14, Folder II.A.31)
    - Profile: "Moving with the Flow," Henry Geldzahler, 11/6/1971; [Original folder title "Henry Geldzahler and the Sixties"] List of Met American Painting and Sculpture purchases of 20th c. art from 1967-1970; typescript of NEA first five years report, correspondence from Shirley Woodward, George Heard Hamilton and Sydney J. Freedberg in response to interview requests from CT; offprints, news clippings, tear sheets, press releases and research notes. (Box 14, Folder II.A.32)
    - Profile: "Moving with the Flow," Henry Geldzahler, 11/6/1971; Tear sheets of Profile, typescript draft (3/18/1971). (Box 14, Folder II.A.33)
    - Onward and Upward with the Arts: "Maybe a Quantum Leap" Earth Art, 2/5/1972; 1 ACS Robert Smithson-CT (9/8/1971) [re:Spiral Jetty] Articles, news clippings, press release, reader correspondence, gallery pamphlets and brochure, draft typescript with hand edits (n.d). (Box 14, Folder II.A.34)
    - Onward and Upward with the Arts: "Maybe a Quantum Leap" Earth Art, 2/5/1972; [Original folder title: "Christo Valley Curtain"] 1 ACS Howard Junker-CT (n.d.) [re: earthworks] 2 ACS Jeanne-Claude and Christo-CT (12/28/1970, 1/3/1970?) [re: holiday greetings] 3 ALS Christo-CT (n.d., 11/19/1970, 6/17/1970) [re: Valley Curtain planning and specifications] Research notes of interviews with Jan Van der Marck and Christo, press releases from the Valley Curtain Corporation, news clippings, exhibition pamphlet of Valley Curtain documentation, The Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, expenses Photographs of preparatory drawings and final installation. (Box 14, Folder II.A.35)
    - Profile: "All Pockets Open," Jonas Mekas, 1/6/1973; 1 TLS Jonas Mekas-CT (4/21/1972) Contacts list, film brochures, news clippings by and about Mekas, research notes, photocopies of correspondence received by Mekas, expenses. (Box 14, Folder II.A.36)
    - Profile: "All Pockets Open," Jonas Mekas, 1/6/1973; Tear sheets of Profile, typescript with hand edits. (Box 14, Folder II.A.37)
    - Profile: "The Black People of Bridgehampton," Bridgehampton, Long Island, 9/10/1973; Correspondence from residents, report of concerned parents committee, various notes on contacts and questions, news clippings. (Box 14, Folder II.A.38)
    - Profile: "The Black People of Bridgehampton," Bridgehampton, Long Island, 9/10/1973; Typescript draft with hand edits (11/30/1972). (Box 14, Folder II.A.39)
    - Profile: "The Rose in the Eye Looked Pretty Fine," Georgia O'Keeffe, 3/4/1974; 1 ACS Georgia O'Keeffe-Unknown (n.d.) 3 TLS Georgia O'Keeffe-CT (8/9, 9/7, and 12/10/1973, 5/7/1974) [re: arrangements for CT visit, response to draft of article, and various other thoughts] 1 TLS Virginia F. Robertson [assistant to O'Keeffe]-CT (8/29/1973) [re: arrangements for visit] Biographical notes, bibliographies, photocopies of secondary materials, photocopy of two-page typescript of O'Keeffe recollections, some letters in response to Profile. (Box 14, Folder II.A.40)
    - Profile: "The Rose in the Eye Looked Pretty Fine," Georgia O'Keeffe, 3/4/1974; Tear sheets of Profile, typescript draft with hand edits (n.d.), full-page advertisement for TNY using O'Keeffe Profile, expenses, news clippings and magazine article from after O'Keeffe's death. (Box 14, Folder II.A.41)
    - A Reporter at Large: "Thinking in Time" Alexander Marshack, 4/22/1974; 1 photocopy TLS Alexander Marshack-CT (n.d.) [re: pre-publication history of Marshack's book The Roots of Civilization] News clippings, articles, magazines on archeology and cave art; reader and research correspondence. (Box 15, Folder II.A.42)
    - A Reporter at Large: "Thinking in Time" Alexander Marshack, 4/22/1974; 4 TLS Alexander Marshack-CT (4/16, 5/5, 5/26/1973, 3/31/1974) [re: contacts, research information, etc.] Correspondence from professors and academics regarding CT's research Interview summaries and transcripts, portions of manuscript draft; contact list and bibliographic notes; copies of correspondence received by Marshack; news clippings, articles, book excerpts; copy of paper by Marshack, "Olmec Mosaic Pendant," (1973). (Box 15, Folder II.A.43)
    - A Reporter at Large: "Thinking in Time" Alexander Marshack, 4/22/1974; Articles, news clippings, promotional pages and other materials regarding The Roots of Civilization, list of contacts, expenses, tear sheets of article. (Box 15, Folder II.A.44)
    - Profile: "Look to the Things Around You," Paul Strand, 9/16/1974; 1 TLS John Dunn-CT (n.d.) [re: factual inaccuracies in Profile concerning Elmer Davis and Pare Lorentz, see folder I.33 for correspondence from Lorentz on subject] 1 TLS Henwar Rodakiewicz-CT (10/17/1974) [re: same as above] 2 TLS Ralph Steiner-CT (7/28/1973, n.d.) [re: interview for Profile, earlier letter typed on same leaf as CT letter to Steiner] 1 ALS Hazel Strand-CT (09/14/1974) 8 ALS Paul Strand-CT (8/21/1973-1/24/1974, 2 n.d.) [re: CT's visits, reviews of article draft, other matters] [Note: letters from the Strands are signed variously Hazel and Paul, Paul and Hazel, P., etc., but the individual authors can be distinguished by their hands] Obituary, news clippings, articles, research notes, photocopy of typescript report Strand gave at the International Congress of Cinema (9/49), gloss of interview with Ralph Steiner and page of recollections in Steiner's hand, contacts list. (Box 15, Folder II.A.45)
    - Profile: "Look to the Things Around You," Paul Strand, 9/16/1974; Full-page advertisement for TNY using Strand Profile, typescript draft with hand edits, expenses, assignment of copyright for Profile. (Box 15, Folder II.A.46)
    - Profile: "Good Cooking," Julia Child, 12/23/1974; 1 ALS Rosemary Manell-TNY (9/14/1974) 1 ALS Julia Child-CT (4/20/n.y.) Contact lists, business cards, book of recipes by Child produced for the benefit of the Presbyterian Hospital Medical Center, San Francisco, interview and bibliographical notes, articles, photocopy of speech given by Child and of letters sent to WGBH. (Box 15, Folder II.A.47)
    - Profile: "Good Cooking," Julia Child, 12/23/1974; Summaries of television episodes, press releases on live cooking demonstrations, news clippings, correspondence from Alfred A. Knopf regarding Child's book sales, carbon copy of typescript draft from …Art of French Cooking, copies of Child's fan mail. (Box 15, Folder II.A.48)
    - Profile: "Good Cooking," Julia Child, 12/23/1974; Photocopy of tear sheets of Profile, typescript draft with hand edits (5/17/1974), expenses, full-page advertisement for TNY using Child Profile. (Box 15, Folder II.A.49)
    - Profile: "Time to Think," Robert Wilson, 1/13/1975; Tear sheets, photocopies, performance and festival programs and brochures, correspondence from the Byrd Hoffman Foundation, index to research binder, restaurant menu with doodles (possibly by Wilson?). (Box 15, Folder II.A.50)
    - Profile: "Time to Think," Robert Wilson, 1/13/1975; Tear sheets, interview glosses with Seth S. Faison, Harvey Lichtenstein, Law Lloyd, Robert Wilson and Richard Foreman; expense notes, research notes, programs to Foreman's productions with notes. (Box 15, Folder II.A.51)
    - Profile: "Time to Think," Robert Wilson, 1/13/1975; [Original folder title: "Einstein on the Beach"] News clippings, programs, interview notes with Jan Herman, Golbert Helmsley, Robert Wilson, Philip Glass and notes from visit to the Metropolitan Opera during the staging of Einstein…. (Box 16, Folder II.A.52)
    - Profile: "Time to Think," Robert Wilson, 1/13/1975; News clippings and later materials, tear sheets of Profile, typescript draft with hand edits (1/31/1975). (Box 16, Folder II.A.53)
    - Profile: "Video Visionary," Nam June Paik, 5/5/1975; 2 ACS Nam June Paik-CT (8/12, 12/18/1975) 1 TLS Ann Sperry-CT (6/8/1975) [re: correction to Profile] 1 TLS Douglas Davis-CT (8/20/1974) [incl. Davis article on Paik in Artforum] MoMA press release from Barbara London on Projects: Peter Campus[MoMA Exh. # 1159, December 10, 1976-January 18, 1977], contacts list, various materials regarding video artists Ture Sjlander and Bror Wikstrm, pamphlets and programs on video art, typed corrections by Paik to Profile post-publication, interleaved with annotated tear sheets photocopied typescript by Paik, "Media Planning for the Post Industrial Age" (n.d.), produced for the Rockefeller Foundation [see Paik correspondence in folder II.A.55]. (Box 16, Folder II.A.54)
    - Profile: "Video Visionary," Nam June Paik, 5/5/1975; 1 TLS Nam June Paik-CT (5/29/1974) [re: Rockefeller Foundation report] 1 ALS Nam June Paik-CT (n.d.) Gallery pamphlets, catalogs and ephemera, press releases, news clippings, tear sheets, offprints, document of arts grants to television from the Rockefeller Foundation and other documents pertaining to video art on television, chronology notes. (Box 16, Folder II.A.55)
    - Profile: "Video Visionary," Nam June Paik, 5/5/1975; Later articles and gallery pamphlet, tear sheets of Profile, typescript draft with hand edits (8/2/1974), expenses. (Box 16, Folder II.A.56)
    - Profile: "A Keeper of the Treasure," Betty Parsons, 6/9/1975; 1 TLS Sidney Janis-CT (10/4/1974) [re: Parsons' tenancy and legal history] Contacts list, Parsons Gallery 30th anniversary brochure, two pamphlets on the practice of "Subud", photostats of settlement of lawsuit and other court documents concerning Parsons and Sidney Janis, exhibition catalogue of Parsons' private art collection (Finch College Museum of Art, 1968), typescript draft with hand edits (10/20/1974), drawing of duck signed "Betty Parsons/1972", expenses. (Box 16, Folder II.A.57)
    - Profile: "New Paradigms," Michael Murphy, 1/5/1976; 1 TLS Nancy Williams-CT (1/12/1976) [re: refutation of some claims in Profile] Interview notes, index to interview notes, list of questions, articles, news clippings. (Box 16, Folder II.A.58)
    - Profile: "New Paradigms," Michael Murphy, 1/5/1976; News clippings and articles, Esalen press releases, grant proposal from the Esalen Institute for "American Society in Transition" (9/1974), photocopy of typescript article by Michael Murphy, "Athletes in the Games of Philosophy: Mystical States and Extraordinary Powers in the Practice of Sport" (n.d.), research notes. (Box 16, Folder II.A.59)
    - Profile: "New Paradigms," Michael Murphy, 1/5/1976; Later news clipping, tear sheets of Profile, typescript draft with hand edits (1/13/1975). (Box 16, Folder II.A.60)
    - Profile: "The Moods of a Stone," Tatyana Grossman, 6/7/1976; 1 TLS Tatyana Grossman-CT [corrections to draft of Profile] Booklet from Tamarind Lithography Workshop, Inc., tabloid-sized newsprint catalogue to Jasper Johns Lithographs[MoMA Exh. # 951, December 22, 1970-May 3, 1971], interview notes, draft of manuscript, lists of artists and dates from Universal Limited Art Editions (ULAE), photocopy of Barnett Newman's preface to his 18 Cantos, unsigned corrections and emendations to draft of Profile on Grossman's letterhead, research notes, typescript article on Grossman by Laura B. Thurston (1/9/1974). (Box 16, Folder II.A.61)
    - Profile: "The Moods of a Stone," Tatyana Grossman, 6/7/1976; [Original folder title: "Prints"] Responses to Profile from other printers (one with specific rebuttal of assertions,) obituary and news clippings, typescript draft by CT of memorial tribute to Grossman (7/8/1982), interview notes, press releases, photocopy of recollections of Grossman by Robert Motherwell. (Box 16, Folder II.A.62)
    - Profile: "Ridiculous," Charles Ludlam, 11/15/1976; Tear sheets of Profile, typescript draft with hand edits, research notes, theater programs, news clippings,The Drama Review 18:2 (June, 1974) with articles by Charles Ludlam and Richard Foreman. (Box 17, Folder II.A.63)
    - Onward and Upward with the Arts: "Running Fence," Christo, 3/28/1977; News clippings, curriculum vitae of Christo and Jeanne-Claude, official photographs of Wrapped Reichstag and fact sheet of project, research notes, typescript draft with hand edits (10/12/1976). (Box 17, Folder II.A.64)
    - Onward and Upward with the Arts: "Running Fence," Christo, 3/28/1977; 1 TLS CT-The New York Times (10/20/1980) [re: rebuttal to editorial opposition to Christo's gates project for Central Park] 1 TLS Jeanne-Claude and Christo-CT (n.d.) [on forwarded letter form the California Coastal Zone Conservation Commission re:Running Fence] 1 TLS Christo-CT (4/22/1976) News clippings, fact sheets and Christo project descriptions, press releases, photographs of preparatory drawings. (Box 17, Folder II.A.65)